<content>
	<partners>
			<partnersName>EUROPEAN CHAMBER OF COMMERCE OF THE PHILIPPINES (ECCP)</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/eccp.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>eccp</idName>
			<info>
				European Chamber of Commerce of the Philippines (ECCP) is a bilateral foreign chamber 
				that promotes European interests in the Philippines as well as Philippine interests in Europe. 
				With more than 700 members, ECCP offers a strong business network that potentially translates 
				to multiple business opportunities. It is a unique organization that offers membership as well 
				as professional services to members and clients.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.eccp.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.eccp.com/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>ISRAEL CHAMBER OF COMMERCE OF THE PHILIPPINES (ICCP)</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/iccp.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>iccp</idName>
			<info>
				Israel Chamber of Commerce of the Philippines (ICCP) is a newly transformed private, independent and non-profit organization coming from a solid and respectable heritage of the Philippine Israel Business Association (PIBA). ICCP’s mission is to encourage business-to-business networking within the Philippines and bilateral trade between Philippines and Israel. It aims to serve businesses through the participation of its members in promoting their long-term objectives, while contributing to the civic, social and economic development of the Philippines. 
			</info>
			<info2>
				As an ICCP member, you will be “in the frontline” of the foremost business groups of the country. We have successfully established a network of networks joining with different foreign chambers, Philippine Chamber of Commerce &amp; Industry and other industry – group-focused trade and business organization. You will also be able to attend as a Member, a wide range of exclusive forums, seminars, tutorials and business luncheons. These events are regularly attended, and even arranged, by outstanding members of the local business community. 
			</info2>
			<linkTitle>www.iccp.ph</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.iccp.ph/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>THE F.A.C. (FOREIGN ASSISTANCE CENTER PHILIPPINES) OFFICE</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/fac.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>fac</idName>
			<info>
				The F.A.C. (Foreign Assistance Center Philippines) Office is the first in the Philippines of its sort. The F.A.C. provide all legal residing Foreigners, Retirees, Guests and Investors with their given Rights under the Philippine Laws specifically Immigration Law. We advise, inform or process any necessary Court Procedure to prevent our client from any unlawful Influence or harmful Judgment of the Court. The F.A.C. to make sure, that nobody will fall into the corrupt hand. This statement based upon our Successes for more Security to all Tourist, Retirees and Investors in the Philippines.
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.foreign-assistance-center.com</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.foreign-assistance-center.com/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATION OF THE PHILIPPINES (MAP)</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/map.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>map</idName>
			<info>
				MAP is a 62-year-old management organization whose 800 members represent a cross-section of CEOs, COOs and other top management practitioners from the largest local and multinational companies operating in the Philippines. MAP also counts some top management educators and government officials as its members. 
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.map.org.ph</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.map.org.ph/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>THE PHILIPPINE TOUR OPERATORS ASSOCIATION (PHILTOA)</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/philtoa.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>philtoa</idName>
			<info>
				The Philippine Tour Operators Association (PHILTOA), Inc. is an organization of tour operators and allied members actively involved in the advocacy of responsible tourism. Founded on 12 June 1986, non-stock and non-profit organization. The membership includes travel agencies, hotel, resorts, transportation companies, handicraft stores, and other tourism-oriented establishments and association. 
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.philtoa.org</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.philtoa.org/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>CSR WORLD MAGAZINE</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/csr.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>csr</idName>
			<info>
				CSR World Magazine is the premier publication covering issues and challenges on Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR). Published across all sectors and industries, it is the definitive roadmap that incorporates theory and practice providing case studies that helps public as well as private sectors to identify situations and solutions for the implementation of their CSR policies.
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.csrworldmagazine.com</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.csrworldmagazine.com/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>HOTEL AND RESTAURANT ASSOCIATION OF THE PHILIPPINES</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/hrap.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>hrap</idName>
			<info>
				 The Hotel and Restaurant Association of the Philippines has celebrated its 50th Anniversary in 2001 and likewise was reincorporated as an Association for another 50 years last August 2001. From a handful of owners and managers in 1951 – HRAP has grown into a full-pledged national organization representing the interests and concerns of the Hotel &amp; Restaurant industry in the whole country. 
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.hrap.org.ph</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.hrap.org.ph/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>THE BRITISH CHAMBER OF COMMERCE OF THE PHILIPPINES</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/bccp.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>bcc</idName>
			<info>
				The British Chamber of Commerce Philippines (BCCP) is an independent, non-profit membership organization whose primary objective is to support the development of its members’ business and social interests in the British and Philippine communities, helping them achieve their objectives. Founded in 1997 as the British Business Association, we became a British Chamber of Commerce in 2001. Today, we represent over 200 member companies and individuals with a membership network of over 400 entrepreneurs and senior executives of multinational corporations and SMEs. 
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.britcham.org</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://britcham.org.ph/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>STARBUCKS</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/starbucks.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>starbucks</idName>
			<info>
				December 4, 1997, the Philippines had its first taste of the Starbucks Experience with its very first branch at the 6750 Ayala Building in Makati City. Starbucks has since won the hearts of the Filipinos. 
				The opening of the 6750 Ayala store marked an important milestone in our history – the Philippines became the third market to open outside North America. 
				The tradition of warm hospitality, constant need for connection, and love for coffee – these are the qualities that make Starbucks Coffee and the Filipino people a great culture fit. 
			</info>
			<linkTitle>philippines.starbucks.com</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://philippines.starbucks.com/en-US/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>TOWER CLUB</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/tc.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>tc</idName>
			<info>
				The Tower Club is a highly-exclusive, premium business club for the country's top executives. With members comprised of notable leaders and society figures, the Club maintains supremacy through our ability to address the needs of today's businessman. We do this by placing membership satisfaction as our only goal and we ensure this by providing a distinct brand of service, technologically advanced facilities and culinary excellence. To enhance the experience, we also create events and offers targeted towards our members' interest
			</info>
			<linkTitle>towerclub.com.ph</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.towerclub.com.ph/</link>
	</partners>

	<partners>
			<partnersName>AMCHAM PHILIPPINES</partnersName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/partners/amcham.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>amcham</idName>
			<info>
				The year was 1797 and the place was the sixth largest city in the United States – Salem, Massachusetts. On May 22nd of that year, the first American ship returned from a nearly non-stop voyage from Manila with the first cargo of Philippine products. The vessel was the brig “Astrea” on her maiden voyage. She had sailed from Salem to Manila in 164 days and then returned in 163 days with a cargo of sugar, pepper and indigo. Now, more than 200 years later, we see the continuing growth of trade between the two countries.
			</info>
			<linkTitle>www.amchamphilippines.com</linkTitle>	
			<link>http://www.amchamphilippines.com/</link>
	</partners>

</content>