<content>
	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>AYALA LAND</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/ayalaland.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>ayalaland</idName>
			<info>
				Ayala Land transformed the Philippine landscape with the nation's premier business district over five decades ago. As the largest, most experienced, and most trusted company in its field, Ayala Land leads the burgeoning real estate industry in the Philippines with prime residential and commercial developments.

				Ayala Land Premier carries the heritage of Ayala Land. From high-rise condominiums to suburban environments and leisure communities, Ayala Land Premier developments are true testaments to high-quality living. Heralded for their prestige, choice location, and unrivaled land value appreciation, each development guarantees prime locations and desired addresses.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.ayalalandpremier.com.ph</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.ayalalandpremier.com.ph</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Avida</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/avida.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>avida</idName>
			<info>
				Since it developed the vast tract of swamp land that is now the bustling city of Makati, Ayala Corporation has become a name indelibly etched in the minds of Filipinos as a visionary developer of land, as a builder of dreams.

				Yet, it was only in 1988 when Ayala Corporation spun off its real estate division into a separate company, giving birth to Ayala Land Inc. (ALI).

				ALI then was primarily associated with high-end projects, whether central business districts, commercial centers, or exclusive family residences, found mostly in Makati and Alabang in Muntinlupa City.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.avidaland.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.avidaland.com/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Mandala Spa &amp; Villas | Boracay</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/mandala.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>mandala</idName>
			<info>
				Mandala Spa &amp; Villas is the first choice for discerning travelers to the magical paradise island of Boracay—consistently voted as one of the Top Ten Beaches of the world.

				One of Asia’s finest spa resorts, Mandala Spa &amp; Villas is renowned for its award-winning spa treatments, elegant facilities, healthy cuisine and legendary service. The recipient of numerous prestigious nominations and awards from leading spa journals—including Best Wellness Retreat, Destination Spa of the Year, Spa Retreat of the Year, Spa Treatment of the Year, In-Spa Training of the Year and Best Rejuvenation Program—this idyllic private estate offers luxury villa accommodations and rejuvenating holistic spa therapies in an exclusive tropical sanctuary.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.mandalaspa.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.mandalaspa.com/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Custom Club Makers</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/customclub.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>customclub</idName>
			<info>
				Custom Clubmakers specializes in Custom-fit and Custom-built golf equipment. Founded in 1990 by Barry J. Harris in PengChau, Hong Kong, and was launched in 1998 in the Philippines by Francis S. Go.
				Francis, President of Custom Clubmakers International Philippines, underwent training programs in Hong Kong and the United States before opening their first shop at Shaw Blvd, Mandaluyong City. Custom Clubmakers began providing quality club repairs, clubfittings, retro-fitting and custom-building of golf equipment to both golf professionals and amateurs alike.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.customclubmakersgolf.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.customclubmakersgolf.com/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>San Miguel Corporation</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/sanmiguel.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>sanmiguel</idName>
			<info>
				Established in 1890 as a single-product brewery, San Miguel Corporation (San Miguel) is the Philippines’ largest beverage, food and packaging company. Today, the company has over 100 facilities in the Philippines, Southeast Asia, and China.
				One of the country’s premier business conglomerates, San Miguel’s extensive product portfolio includes over 400 products ranging from beer, hard liquor, juices, basic and processed meats, poultry, dairy products, condiments, coffee, flour, animal feeds and various packaging products.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.sanmiguel.com.ph</linkTitle>
			<link>http://sanmiguel.com.ph</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Sheridan Beach Resort and Spa</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/sheridan.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>sheridan</idName>
			<info>
				Strategically situated in the heart of Sabang Beach, Puerto Princesa City. Sheridan Beach Resort and Spa is a few hundred meters from the Subterranean Underground River (one of the finalists of the Seven Wonders of Nature).
				A member of Preferred Hotel Group under the Sterling Hotels brand, Sheridan Beach Resort and Spa is a world-class luxury resort dedicated in promoting its principles and sustainable eco-tourism.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.sheridanbeachresort.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.sheridanbeachresort.com</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Thunderbird Resorts</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/thunderbird.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>thunderbird</idName>
			<info>
				Thunderbird Resorts is an international property developer of dynamic, themed, and integrated venues that are anchored by casinos. It is a provider of branded casino and hospitality services in Asia and Latin America.

				We operate in: Costa Rica, India, Nicaragua, Peru, Philippines
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.thunderbirdresorts.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.thunderbirdresorts.com</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Volvo Philippines</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/volvo.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>volvo</idName>
			<info>
				Volvo Philippines is the official authorized distributor and dealer of Volvo cars in the Philippines. For 16 years, it has consistently delivered cars that are premium in design, build, fit and finish. They are safe. They are engineered in a way that considers humans and the environment around them. We create the best solutions for traveling together. We consider design as a collaboration between styling and engineering which creates premium cars with a sophisticated content.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.volvo.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.volvo.com</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Chevrolet Philippines</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/chevrolet.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>chevrolet</idName>
			<info>
				The Covenant Car Company Inc. (TCCCI) is a Filipino company with a strong backing of experienced players in the automotive industry led by its Chairman Emeritus, Mr. Richard Lee, whose more than three decades of success in the Philippine automotive industry shall be poured into building and re-capturing the passion for Chevrolet.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.chevy.com.ph</linkTitle>
			<link>http://chevy.com.ph/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>The Medical City</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/medicalcity.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>medicalcity</idName>
			<info>
				The Medical City (TMC) is a tertiary care hospital with over forty years experience in hospital operation and administration. Its world-class health care complex serves some 40,000 in-patients and 400,000 out-patients annually. TMC has a medical staff of over 1,000 physicians who are established experts in their various fields of specialization. This core of professionals is complemented by a 2,200-strong human resource complement, engaged in allied medical, administrative and support services.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.themedicalcity.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://themedicalcity.com/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Forth and Tay</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/forthandtay.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>forthandtay</idName>
			<info>
				Wines from 9 countries, 5 continents and over 20 different grape varietals to suit the most discerning palate
				Forth &amp; Tay is the leading direct merchant of wines and spirits in the Philippines with a portfolio of nearly 300 brands, all of which can be delivered to your home or office at highly competitive prices.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.forthandtay.com</linkTitle>
			<link>http://www.forthtay.com/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
			<sponsorsName>Philippine Retirement Authority</sponsorsName>
			<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/philra.jpg</imageSource>
			<idName>philra</idName>
			<info>
				The Philippine Retirement Authority (PRA) is a government owned and controlled corporation which was created by virtue of
	            Executive Order No. 1037, which was signed by then President Ferdinand E. Marcos, on 04 July 1985. On 31 August 2001, through
	            Executive Order No. 26, the control and supervision of PRA was transferred to the Board of Investments (BOI) from the Office
	            of the President. In November 2009, Department of Tourism Secretary Joseph H. Durano, signed Republic Act No. 9593, otherwise
	            known as Tourism Act of 2009, which transferred the Authority from Board of Investments to the Department of Tourism.
			</info>
			<info2></info2>	
			<linkTitle>www.pra.gov.ph</linkTitle>
			<link>http://pra.gov.ph/</link>
	</sponsors>

	<sponsors>
				<sponsorsName>Rustan's</sponsorsName>
				<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/rustans.jpg</imageSource>
				<idName>rustans</idName>
				<info>
					In the Philippines, the name “RUSTAN’S” is often synonymous with retailing. In its nearly five decades of operations, RUSTAN’S, primarily through its department stores, and additionally through its formidable network of companies, has helped to define the fledging science of retailing in the Philippines and the Southeast Asian region. It boasts a standard of operational and merchandising excellence that is second to none in the world.

					In the Philippines, when looking for a quality product or brand, the first question inevitably asked is often, “Maybe RUSTAN’S has it?,” a subtle testimony to and recognition of the tradition of quality and excellence associated with the name of the group. 
				</info>
				<info2></info2>	
				<linkTitle>www.rustans.com.ph</linkTitle>
				<link>http://www.rustans.com.ph/</link>
		</sponsors>

		<sponsors>
				<sponsorsName>MEGAWORLD CORPORATION</sponsorsName>
				<imageSource>/resources/images/sponsors/megaworld.jpg</imageSource>
				<idName>megaworld</idName>
				<info>
					Megaworld Corporation is the country's leading real estate developer and No. 1 business process and outsourcing (BPO) office developer and landlord in the Philippines. Led by real estate magnate and visionary, Dr. Andrew L. Tan, Megaworld pioneered the LIVE-WORK-PLAY-LEARN township concept in the country. 
				</info>
				<info2></info2>	
				<linkTitle>www.megaworldcorp.com</linkTitle>
				<link>http://www.megaworldcorp.com/</link>
		</sponsors>
</content>